ABOUT

I'm an Integrations Specialist / Full Stack Application Developer with experience working as a UI, UX, & QA engineer, system administrator. Current career goals & objectives include designing and implementing enterprise-scale systems, minimizing costs & maximizing performance of software solutions, improving operational efficiency of organizations, learning new technologies to overcome business challenges. Other professional interests include analytics, data science, fintech / investing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Babson College

Integrations Specialist

Babson Park, MA Jul 2019 – present

- I write integrations for a variety of systems using SOAP and RESTful web services, APIs, ETL tools, MS SQL Server.
- I work with and help configure Salesforce.com (Sales/HEDA Cloud), Informatica (ICS, DI, APIs), Workday (HCM, Finance, Student), JIRA (on prem), Cvent, SharePoint, Canvas, Blackboard, EMS, Neoload, and other technologies.

Application Developer

Apr 2014 - Jul 2019

- Designed, developed, and maintained complex, dynamic, enterprise-level web applications using Adobe ColdFusion/Fusebox, Java, PHP/Drupal, C#/.NET, JS, CSS.
- Wrote custom two-way web services and data feeds to integrate internal data stores and systems with a variety of third party applications and tools.

Software Developer Co-op / Application Developer Intern

May 2012 - Apr 2014

- Created and maintained dynamic web applications for the Babson Portal a platform of over 150 custom written tools with 2,000,000+ lines of code; researched, proposed, and integrated new software solutions.
- Developed custom system workflows (XML), services, and events (JellyScript) in JIRA, performed system administration of the Atlassian stack (JIRA, Confluence) including data back-up, indexing, and restoring, system troubleshooting, patching, etc.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Advanced knowledge of Adobe ColdFusion, t-SQL, JavaScript, CSS, XML/HTML, ETL tools (Informatica, SSIS), SOAP and RESTful web services, JIRA, Confluence.

Intermediate knowledge of C/C#, .NET, Java, PHP, Drupal, Force.com platform, SOQL/APEX/Visualforce, Workbench, git, Workday, Cvent, VSS.

Familiarity with Assembly (MASM), Python, Perl, Objective C/Swift, most flavors of shell scripting, SharePoint, Selenium, CrazyEgg, Mendix, Neoload, Laserfiche, webRTC, webVR, MEAN stack.

EDUCATION

Babson College

Babson Park, MA

F. W. Olin Graduate School of Business

Sep 2018 - Dec 2019

Master of Science in Business Analytics

Babson College

Babson Park, MA

F. W. Olin Graduate School of Business

May 2016 – Aug 2018

Master of Business Administration (MBA), Business Analytics concentration

Wentworth Institute of Technology

Boston, MA

College of Engineering and Technology
Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Sep 2011 – <u>Apr 2014</u> GPA: 3.82

Dean's List (2011-2014), graduated with honors: magna cum laude

- Tau Alpha Pi Honor Society, Applied Math minor, 2014 Annual Awards Recipient

- Wentworth Community Scholarship and Wentworth Merit Scholarship Recipient

University of Tyumen (transferred out)

Tyumen, Russia

Institute of Mathematics and Computer Science

Sep 2008 - May 2011

BS/MS in Software Development and Information Systems Administration

- Full Tuition Scholarship
- Outstanding Incoming Class Award Recipient

CONFERENCES, WORKSHOPS, SEMINARS, AND HACKATHONS

- Eliassen Group Agile Foundations 3-day onsite training, May 2019 (Wellesley, MA)
- The Citizens Challenge FinTech Hackathon, Jul 2018 (Boston, MA)
- Babson Finance Conference, Mar 2018 (Boston, MA)
- TERMINALFOUR Advanced Web Developer, 3-day onsite training, Jan 2018 (Wellesley, MA)
- Reality Virtually Hack @ MIT, Oct 2017 (Cambridge, MA) Project: WebVR Checkout
- Programmatic Development Using Apex and Visualforce (DEV450), Sep 2017 (Boston, MA)
- Hacking for Good @ HBS, Jun 2017 (Boston, MA)
- InformaticaWorld, May 2017 (San Francisco, CA)
- HackWITus @ WIT, Mar 2017 (Boston, MA) Project: WebArm
- AT&T WebRTC Boston Coding Workshop, May 2016 (Boston, MA)
- Future of Wearables Scramble™ @ Babson, Apr 2016 (Wellesley, MA)
- Salesforce World Tour, Apr 2016, May 2017, Apr 2018 (Boston, MA)
- Boston Code Camps (24 27), Nov 2015, 2016 & Mar 2016, 2017 (Cambridge, MA)
- Workday Higher Education Summit, Oct 2015 (Wellesley, MA)
- Dyn's Hackademy, May 2015 (Manchester, NH) Project: Conversion Wars Web App
- NeoLoad 3-day training, Feb 2015 (Waltham, MA)
- Laserfiche 4-day training, Sep 2014 (Wellesley, MA)
- Mendix 3-day onsite training, Aug 2014
- Dyn's Hackademy, May 2014 (Manchester, NH) Project: DWC Boy Scouts iOS App

VOLUNTEER SERVICE AND ACTIVITIES

Commonwealth Kitchen

Non-voting member of the board, Babson Board Fellow

Babson

- Advanced Degree Employee Resource Group (ERG) Chair
- Analytics and Race Conversations ERGs member
- Community Learning Day (CLD) Committee Member
- Entrepreneurial Thought & Action (ET&A) Award Selection Committee Member
- "Kids on Campus Day" Garden Session Volunteer
- Commencement Volunteer

Wentworth

- Admissions Blogger, Admissions Office
- Web Application Developer, Career Services
- International Student Ambassador, International Student Services
- President's Host, **President's Host Society**
 - o Represented the Institute at various events, on and off campus
 - Served as an ambassador of public relations in various supporting roles
 - Promoted Wentworth's academic programs, services and student activities
- Alternative Spring Break Volunteer, Community Partnership Office
 - Focused on environmental work in the Biscayne and the Everglades National Parks, FL
 - Worked with wounded birds at the Florida Keys Wild Bird Sanctuary, FL
 - Worked with animals at Florida Monkey Forest Zoo, Key Largo, FL
- Note Taker for a Disabled Student, Counseling Center & Disability Services Partnership

AFFILIATIONS AND PERSONAL INTERESTS

- I sit on the board of a local nonprofit as a Babson Board Fellow.
- I've been a member of TAΠ (<u>Tau Alpha Pi</u>, Massachusetts Alpha Chapter) the professional honor society for engineering technology since 2013.
- Occasionally, I participate in the local Boston technology meetups, hackathons, and user group activities such as BNT (Boston New Technology), <u>Boston AUG</u> (Atlassian User Group), <u>Code</u> for Boston Hack Nights, and others.
- I am a frequent Kiva.org lender and encourage you to become one.
- Outside of my day-to-day duties as a developer I enjoy cycling, creating and playing music, learning new things, and generally expanding my horizons.